Your Highness
Ваше Высочество
My men will follow all the way
Мои люди будут сопровождать вас до конца пути
No one can mistreat you
никто не посмеет обидеть вас
Teacher Yu
Учитель Ю
Some things
коечто
Hear but don't take to heart
стоит просто пропустить мимо ушей
As long as one lives
Быть живым
That's what matters most
важнее всего
This subject
Это я
Has brought trouble upon Your Highness
навлёк беду на Ваше Высочество
I hope Teacher Yu
Берегите себя учитель Ю
Will take care
Береги себя
Your Highness, take care
И Вы тоже берегите себя Ваше Высочество
What are you doing?
Эй Что вы тут делаете
Your students
Ученики
Thank Your Highness for your grace
выражаем благодарность за Вашу милость Ваше Высочество
Thank you, Your Highness
Благодарим Ваше Высочество
For protecting our teacher's life
Благодарим принца за спасение жизни учителя
If there is an opportunity in the future
Если когдалибо появится шанс мы обязательно отплатим за это великое благодеяние
We will repay Your Highness's great kindness
обязательно отплачу за великую милость
Enough
Довольно
You are all pillars of Great Xuan's future
вы все  опора будущего великой империи Сюань
Rise quickly
Поднимайтесь
All of you, rise
все поднимайтесь
This matter
Этот случай
I hope you all take it as a warning
надеюсь станет уроком для всех вас
I will also take it as a warning
и для меня тоже
Your students
студенты
Will remember Your Highness's teachings
Запомним наставления Вашего Высочества